http://www.fettbrosperformance.com/privacy

HomeShopRide TechShop TalkPrivacyContact UsMoreHomeShopRide TechShop TalkPrivacyContact UsHomeShopRide TechShop TalkPrivacyContact Us
Privacy Policy  Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect?When filling out forms or registering for warranty, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details.Why do we collect this data?We collect this data as pertinent to the use of contacting you for customer service, emailing you with special offers (if you’ve “opted-in”), and as required by law for warranty or informing about safety defects.Purpose and Reason We Collect Your Data?   When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you place an order, fill out a form, or enter information on our site.Financial Information.We do not retain your financial information beyond the time it takes for it to clear. If you order online, we use PayPal and do not retain any financial information. PayPal has its own privacy policy found here: https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-fullHow do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:· To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.· To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.· Fulfill your orderHow long do we retain your data?We retain your data for as long as we are required by law to report safety defects or honor our warranty. For surveys, contacting us, or otherwise filling out our data forms, we retain your information for as long as the law states for IRS or corporate purposes. This can be six (6) months or up to seven (7) years.How can I retrieve, remove, or change the PII data collected?You can contact us at the address and phone number below and we can help you through the request.How do we protect visitor information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use cookies to:· Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.· Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled, but it won't affect the users’ experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless required by law. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.GoogleWe use Google Analytics to track site usage and traffic. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which you can read here: https://policies.google.com/privacyCalifornia Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:· Users can visit our site anonymously· Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page· Users are able to change their personal information by calling us or sending an email to marketing@towmaster.com How does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under 13.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:· Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.· Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders· We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.· Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:· NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses· Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way· Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters· Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.· Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly· Allow users to unsubscribe within the email If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at· Follow the instructions within the email. Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Fett Brothers Performance11684 Woods DriveFrazee, MN 56544218-334-3388fettbros@loretel.net
Copyright © 2020 Fett Brothers Performance - All Rights Reserved.PrivacyContact UsTerms
